Reviews found in longest blob: 178

=== 1. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 10 months ago ===
    Dear Siddhesh, Thank you for your feedback and three-star rating. We're thrilled you enjoyed our Broaster Platter, especially the crispy fried chicken, juicy kebabs, and stir-fried prawns. The rum-infused chicken pizza's unique twist was a delight! We're sorry to hear that we fell short of a four or five-star rating. Please let us know how we can improve your experience on your next visit. We look

=== 2. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 4 months ago ===
    Dear Fareeda Ibrahim, Thank you for your feedback. We appreciate your visit and are glad you enjoyed our food. Well definitely look into adjusting the music volume to ensure a more comfortable dining experience for everyone. Your comfort matters to us! Regards,

=== 3. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 3 months ago ===
    Dear Prakash Moorthy, thank you for your feedback! We're thrilled you enjoyed our food and ambience. We appreciate your suggestion about the music volumewe'll definitely take it into consideration to ensure a better experience next time. Looking forward to welcoming you back! Regards,

=== 4. Edited | 2 years ago ===
    Dine in | Dinner | 1,4001,600 A quick getaway for a weekend evening. A blend of Good Food, Live Music and DJ music. The Vibe of the place is perfect for one who wants to dance their heart out. More 1

=== 5. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 6. Edited | 3 years ago ===
    Food: Broaster - First time my hands on a boiled roasted (Broasted) chicken!! Fricking amazing with the layered crunchy skin, marinade, and tender meat!! Went well More 1

=== 7. Edited | 5 years ago ===
    Been twice to this place.We visited one which is in Satara plaza,Palm beach road. Again, we used Dineout for booking, and to avail the discount also the restaurant was offering 20% (offer vaild). Even without discounts, overall menu prices

=== 8. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    One of the best places to hangout and chill in Vashi, Navi Mumbai. The ambience is well lit, live and peepy, and not gloomy and dark as most places. The food is no doubt a fried chicken afficiando's dream. Good Food, Great Ambience, Great

=== 9. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Ambience is good..... Music is bit loud... I like their idea of using baseball cap as cover for bulbs...

=== 10. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Located at Satra Plaza On Palm Beach Road. This is one of the best place to hangout and have some mouthwatering fried chicken. More 1 tuhina singh Local Guide59 reviews392 photos 8 years ago I have been here so many times in the last month alone. The place is great with live music and nice ambience. The staff is helpful and the offer on drinks are great. Excellent place for after office hang outs.

=== 11. Edited | 8 years ago ===
    Brand New Place in Vashi (Navi Mumbai) and it's brilliant. The menu is pretty diverse and also has quite a lot of Veg options. The Fried chicken is Superb. They have some crazy Burgers as well. Alcohol is 1 + 1 all day long all days of the More 5 yiyasha Local Guide126 reviews360 photos 6 years ago I loved the ambience, the interior, the decor.

=== 12. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    It used to be one of the happening places in Navi Mumbai. Things have changed now. GBC suits your pocket and is also very lovely at the same time. Food is good (starters), varieties of Ale are even better. I wish it had a dance floor with a

=== 13. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    The best thing about GBC is it's ambience it was decorated with different art of sports,film industry, quotes on wall frame,etc. As it's name suggest chicken of this place was supposed to be good but I didn't

=== 14. Edited | 5 years ago ===
    So yeah! It is located in Satra Plaza on the first level. More 6

=== 15. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations.

=== 16. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    I heard a lot about it but never got a chance to visit this place earlier, but this New Year one of my friend threw his birthday party here and i was literally cursing myself what was i waiting for. The food is awesome, the ambience is awesome and everything is awesome.

=== 17. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 18. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    GBC in Satra Plaza is well known for their food and drinks ,it's an Amazing restaurant located in 1st floor of Satra plaza , Vashi . Genuine Broaster Chicken is America's one of the Oldest Food Joint and has serve

=== 19. Edited | 8 years ago ===
    Great place with good food options...!!!

=== 20. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 21. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    This is a chill out place where one can enjoy it's food and relax in the atmo. Staff is co-operative and it is very much famous for it's chicken quality and taste.

=== 22. Edited | 2 years ago ===
    The best cozy place to unwind yourself from daily hustle .No second thought for ladies who are willing to hang out in a safe and nice place. Their fir pizza and LIT is a must try for people with sweet tooth brownie is on point. More 4

=== 23. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 24. Edited | 3 years ago ===
    Dine in | Lunch | 1,2001,400 The place was wonderful. Tasty food. Had a wonderful day. Would like to visit more often.

=== 25. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    They serve a variety of authentic American delicacies like chicken burgers, pastas, fried chicken wings, shakes, iced teas, cocktails..Indian food is also available

=== 26. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Try chicken platters they are worth eating

=== 28. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Have been here many times and its always a great experience. Food and service is good. Ambiance is also very nice. Nice place to hangout with friends. 1 sohail ansari Local Guide121 reviews174 photos 4 years ago Dine in | Dinner Price is too high compared to the food's taste, ambiance and service is good. A one time visit restaurant

=== 29. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 31. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 7 months ago ===
    Dear Sameer, We're sorry to hear about your experience during our happy hours. Our intention is to make our customers happy, not fool them. We'll look into this matter and ensure it doesn't happen again. Regards,

=== 32. Edited | 8 years ago ===
    Good place to have fried chicken, probably the best in Mumbai. Fast service, good place to host a party. 1

=== 33. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    In short Best place for chicken Dips served with chicken are very tasty Hover to react Nazia sheriff 8 reviews8 photos 3 years ago Dine in | Dinner | 8001,000 Randomly visited this place for dinner and I think it was the best decision. Excellent food with good portion size and quality! Ive never had such juicy chicken in a long time. The management and staff were very courteous and the service Mor

=== 35. Edited | 8 years ago ===
    Good place but staff keeps peeping on your platter I feel awkward. I have been many places but never had that kind of experience Hover to react Avantika Singh 4 reviews a year ago The food is good. Alcohol not so great. The DJ on 27.09.2024 was the worst and a hypocrite. He will play music of an artist and then when requested for another music of the same artist  he wont

=== 37. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Awesome food and Heaven for non vegetarians and decent options for Vegetarians bit tastes quite average... You get good beer options here. Music is loud but one of the few places which offers live match screening in this area. Service can be much better. Decent crowd... Overall an okay place 2

=== 38. Edited | 4 years ago ===
    Good place to hangout with friends. Nice ambiance and a bonus for people having booze because of the Happy hours.

=== 39. Edited | 8 years ago ===
    Good place to hangout. Nice ambiance and music

=== 40. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 42. Edited | 8 years ago ===
    One of the best place to try some great fried chicken. Good place to hangout with friends chill have some drinks and great food. The place is crowded sometimes. Ambiance is good live sport screening available. Will visit again soon. More 3

=== 43. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Pretty interior design and playlist. Wish the burgers were bigger for the price. Pasta was goood. So were the platters/starters. Great dips. Also, the environment during lunch was very quiet compared to the ambience in the evening on weekends or match days with good music and drinks.

=== 44. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Great place for a nice dinner with friends/family. Location is Satra Plaza, which is the hub for all sorts and numbers of restaurants.

=== 46. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 47. Edited | 3 years ago ===
    Dine in | Lunch | 400600 I recently had the pleasure of dining at Genuine Broaster Chicken in Navi Mumbai and was thoroughly impressed with my experience.

=== 49. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    A new place that has come up at Vashi. Worth trying for the interesting set up of seating arrangements and also the roof that catches your eye for its Innovativeness. Personally felt the place was too congested for the number of tables put

=== 50. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 9 months ago ===
    Hi Sahil ji , Thank you for taking the time to share your concerns about your recent visit to our Genuine Broaster Chicken outlet . We're truly sorry to hear that you didn't receive the one plus one offer as advertised . We understand how frustrating it can be when expectations aren't met, and we're committed to making it right . At Genuine Broaster Chicken, we pride ourselves on being transparent

=== 51. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Located at Satra Plaza, first floor. Entire interior is so unique consisting of helmets, different frames, lights, different styles of seating arrangements. Together I liked their ambience which helped me to get refresh after tiring work.

=== 52. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 53. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 54. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    GBC this restaurant is located in Vashi satra plaza 1st floor.Amazing restaurant with perfect location to attract the crowd. Here they have an amazing ambience with nice and attractive lights and an

=== 55. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations.

=== 56. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 9 months ago ===
    Dear Harish TM, We apologize for the disappointing experience with the free drinks offered through Dineout. We strive to provide our customers with the best service and quality, and we regret that we fell short during your visit. Your feedback is valuable to us, and we will take necessary steps to ensure that such incidents do not occur in the future. Regards,

=== 57. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Its nice place for drink n food n chilling. Cool place. I spc go for its wings. I never had such awesome wings anywhere. Highly recommended. Hover to react francis vincent 6 reviews 6 years ago Drinks, broasted chicken, chicken salad and fries with kheema were the things I had... The first were good enough for me not to complain.... Fries with keema didn't turn out to be that good... Not because o

=== 58. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Great place to chill and hang around. The live music is absolutely stunning, makes for a great Friday evening. Strongly recommend!

=== 59. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Awesome place to hangout. Love the ambience, their offers.

=== 61. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Tasty food with amazing offers!

=== 62. Edited | 3 years ago ===
    Dine in | Lunch | 400600 A place with a different ambience. Good burgers and grills. Their Happy fried chicken and oero milkshake are worth a try More Hover to react savli patil 8 reviews 3 years ago Dine in | Dinner | 600800 Been going there since 3 years. Amazing food and ambience is so much fun  Order type:

=== 65. Edited | 4 years ago ===
    It's chill place to hangout, fun atmosphere. The fried chicken is the best thing out there

=== 66. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Cozy place with rocking music.. food is nice.. service is little slow.. Otherwise very good place to hang out with friends Hover to react Rakesh Bomma 10 reviews1 photo

=== 68. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Very nice place, tasty food n value for money. Live band on weekends will make your day!

=== 71. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Great food, on the night

=== 72. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations.

=== 73. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Harmeet Singh 3 reviews4 photos 8 years ago Amazing ambience, great crowd, delicious food, definitely worth your time. Hover to react RAHUL KUMAR 8 reviews9 photos 3 years ago Great food, great ta

=== 74. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 75. Edited | 4 years ago ===
    Dine in | Dinner It's a great place for chicken lovers as you mainly get dishes related with fast food and chicken.

=== 79. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Amazing place for a group of 4-5 people! This place serves the best fried chicken!

=== 80. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Good food and ambience, nice place to hangout with friends and grab a drink.

=== 81. Edited | 2 years ago ===
    Dine in | Lunch | 600800 Broaster Chicken was an outstanding restaurant for getting a better and different taste. Really loved it  More 1

=== 82. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations.

=== 83. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    I tried Broaster chicken, jumbo platter..loved it. Its a costly place bt worth if u go through eatigo app with a 50% off.

=== 84. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 85. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    What a lovely restaurant, good food and service and atmosphere, definitely hope to go back.

=== 86. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Good place to visit for chicken lovers

=== 88. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 92. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Ever carve for crispy fried chicken do visit best goes with chilled beer

=== 93. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Grt place , If chicken is love u should visit this place ,

=== 95. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 96. Edited | 5 years ago ===
    Great Ambience with old used item theme! Found quite unique!

=== 98. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Great place, nice offers running with good ambiance.

=== 99. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 7 months ago ===
    Dear Kammeta, Thank you for taking the time to leave us a positive review and a five-star rating! We're thrilled to hear that you enjoyed your meal at Genuine Broaster Chicken in Navi Mumbai. Our team works hard to ensure that every dish we serve is up to our high standards, and your feedback means a lot to us. We hope to see you again soon! Regards,

=== 100. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 101. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 103. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Ambience and the food makes it the best hangout spot Hover to react Seshu S 14 reviews 8 years ago Its a fake broasted

=== 104. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Very nice place with good food!

=== 107. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 108. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 109. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Great Ambience and really friendly staff!

=== 110. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Awesome ambience, good food

=== 113. Edited | 4 years ago ===
    Good place to hangout with friends.... Hover to react Sushmita Dhanokar 16 reviews 7 years ago Specially for chiken dishes best Hover to react solanki jeetesh 7 reviews

=== 116. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Great food and alcohol Hover to react Harikrishna Varanasi 4 reviews 6 years ago

=== 120. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    The ambience is great. Hover to react prasad 8695 2 reviews 6 years ago

=== 123. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 125. Edited | 6 years ago ===
    Unprofessional stewards Hover to react Vinayak bhagadia 12 reviews3 photos 6 years ago Second home Hover to react Karan Grover 4 reviews 7 years ago

=== 127. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Nice place Hover to react Haadi Jasir 3 reviews 6 years ago

=== 129. Edited | 4 years ago ===
    Dine in | Dinner Order type: Meal type: Hover to react Pranav Kadam 6 photos 7 years ago

=== 131. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 132. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    Hover to react Subhabrata Bose 8 reviews 6 years ago

=== 133. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 3 months ago ===
    Dear Jay Mahimkar, Thank you for your 4-star rating! Were glad you enjoyed your experience at Genuine Broaster Chicken. Your feedback means a lot to us. Hope to serve you again soon! Regards,

=== 134. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 4 months ago ===
    Dear Antoni Boruah, Thank you for your 4-star rating! We're delighted you enjoyed your experience at Genuine Broaster Chicken. Your feedback means a lot to us. Hope to serve you again soon! Regards,

=== 135. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 6 months ago ===
    Dear Abhijit Tadke, thank you so much for your 5-star rating! Were thrilled you enjoyed your experience at Genuine Broaster Chicken. Your support means the world to us. Looking forward to serving you again soon. Regards,

=== 136. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 7 months ago ===
    Dear Atul, We're sorry to hear about your experience. We value your feedback and want to make things right. Please contact us so we can discuss how we can improve. Regards,

=== 137. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 7 months ago ===
    Dear Madhavan, We're thrilled to have earned your five-star rating at Genuine Broaster Chicken in Navi Mumbai. Thank you for your kind review! Regards,

=== 138. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 8 months ago ===
    Dear Omkar, We're thrilled to hear you enjoyed your visit to Genuine Broaster Chicken! Thank you for giving us a five-star rating. We strive to provide an unforgettable dining experience and your feedback means the world to us. Regards,

=== 139. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 9 months ago ===
    Hey Atul, Wow, we're absolutely delighted to hear that you had an amazing experience at Genuine Broaster Chicken! We're thrilled to know that our food and service exceeded your expectations. Your kind words mean the world to us, and we're grateful for customers like you who take the time to share their feedback. We're proud to have a team that's dedicated to providing top-notch service and delicio

=== 140. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 9 months ago ===
    Hey Neelrajeji! Wow, we're thrilled to hear that you had an amazing experience at Genuine Broaster Chicken! Your 5-star review truly made our day! We're grateful for customers like you who take the time to share their positive feedback. We're glad to hear that our food and service exceeded your expectations. Our team works hard to ensure that every customer leaves with a smile on their face, and i

=== 141. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 9 months ago ===
    Dear Falguni ji , Thank you for taking the time to share your thoughts about your recent experience at Genuine Broaster Chicken . We're sorry to hear that your visit didn't quite meet your expectations . We understand that our food and service can be a letdown sometimes, and we're committed to making it right . Can you please share more details about your visit with us? We'd love to know what spec

=== 142. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. prajwal maindan 9 reviews 2 years ago Food: Service:

=== 143. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Aayushya Gupta. 1 review 2 years ago Food: Service: More 1

=== 144. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Rohit Pawar 3 reviews1 photo 2 years ago Takeaway | Brunch | 400600 Order type: Meal type:

=== 145. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Sagar Murli 3 reviews19 photos 2 years ago Dine in | Lunch | 8001,000 Order type: Meal type:

=== 146. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 147. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 148. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for sharing your honest review with us. We apologize for not meeting your expectations. We really hope you give us another chances to improve and serve you better next time. Shravanti M 5 reviews 2 years ago Food: Service:

=== 149. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Aditya Devardekar 4 reviews1 photo 2 years ago Lunch | 400600 Meal type: Price per person:

=== 151. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations.

=== 152. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambience & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Abdullah Qasim 1 review 2 years ago Food: Service: More 1

=== 153. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Abhay Kumar Saini 1 review 2 years ago Food: Service:

=== 154. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 155. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 156. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Ritu Saini 1 review 2 years ago Dine in | Dinner | 2,000+ Order type: Meal type:

=== 157. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Srijit Nair 11 reviews 2 years ago Dine in | Dinner | 600800 Order type: Meal type:

=== 158. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations. We appreciate your support and can't wait to serve you again soon. Affan Ansari 4 reviews22 photos 2 years ago Food: Atmosphere:

=== 159. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 160. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 161. More Hover to react Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 163. Hover to react Sahil Mhatre Local Guide | 4 years ago ===
    Dine in | Other Order type: Meal type:

=== 164. Hover to react Kashish Pathania Local Guide | 4 years ago ===
    Dine in | Dinner Order type: Meal type: Hover to react manoj dorke 7 reviews 4 years ago Dine in | Dinner Order type: Meal type: Hover to react pranav nair 5 reviews2 photos 4 years ago Lunch Meal type: Hover to react Jasir Thendath 1 photo 7 years ago

=== 165. Genuine Broaster Chicken (owner) | 2 years ago ===
    Thank you for taking the time to share your experience! It's fantastic to hear that our food, ambiance & services met your expectations.

=== 167. Isha More | 6 years ago ===
    Amit Kanekar 1 review1 photo 6 years ago lina pradhan 3 reviews 6 years ago

=== 170. Rohit Tupe | 7 years ago ===
    Swanand Tanavade (Kakashi3lite) Local Guide2 reviews 7 years ago

=== 174. Edited | 7 years ago ===
    rishabh joshi 1 review 7 years ago Ketan Gaikwad 1 review 7 years ago

=== 177. Rohit Upadhyay | 7 years ago ===
    Vinit Suvarna 13 reviews 7 years ago

=== 178. Sundeep Tariyal | 7 years ago ===
    rahul rankhambe Local Guide8 reviews64 photos 7 years ago

